ANDRÉ PILASTRI RESUME



▶ I am passionate about Data Science and Computer Vision. With over 5 years of experience developing research projects in Data Science and Computer Vision, my career goal is to master best practices, trends, and new technologies, bringing creative ideas to

>>> STATUS

Managing and coordinating projects the in computer vision and artificial intelligence applications. I conduct practical research with a scientific mindset, and a focus on delivery, working closely with different projects at national and international level with the engineering team to integrate ML algorithms into the platform.

EXPERIENCE

Head of Technology Innovation

GTP Automation, 2018 - 2019/01

- **▶** Development of Industrial Storage solution for the maintenance of stock:
 - Vision Picking Package classification based on AR and Deep Learning;
 - Drone Mapping Empty rack counting using aerial image analysis;
 - Hunter Odometry implementation for drone positioning system;

Assistant Professor

Mato Grosso State University. 2010-2014

- Teacher and Researcher in the disciplinary area of Computer Science, with focus on the following curricular units: algorithms, data structure, and computer graphics;
- ➤ Co-founder: Research Group PIXEL UNEMAT;

EDUCATION

Ph.D. Candidate - Informatics Engineering

FEUP, 2015 / Present

- Thesis (finishing): Complex Networks in Computational Vision Application in the Analysis of Dermatoscopic Images.
 - Focused on developing machine learning models for the diagnosis of skin lesions from medical imaging;
- ▶ Research interests include: medical image processing, computer vision, complex networks, superpixels and deep learning;

Master's Degree, Computer Science

UNESP - São Paulo State University.

- Dissertation: Análise de Multirresolução baseada em Polinômio Potência de Sigmóide -Wavelet;
- In this research presents a technique based on pyramid transforms the PPS and PPS-Wavelet families applied to digital images. The pyramids of images are important techniques used in multiresolution decompositions, applied to computer vision and image processing;

Specialization Course in Project Management -

Centro Universitário Senac, 2009-2010

- Dissertation: Implementation of a high availability Datacenter based on information security.
 - Number of PDUs: 360

CONTACT

- Porto, Portugal
- © +351 910 790 746
- ✓ andre.pilastri@gmail.com
- https://goo.gl/HpLiy2
 - CV Lattes
- in linkedin.com/in/apilastri/
 - github.com/pilastri

FIELDS

Project Management

₽ SCRUM

☆☆☆☆☆☆☆☆☆

</> Software Development **☆☆☆☆☆☆☆☆☆**

Q Consulting **★★★★★★★★★**

₽ DEVOPS

STRENGTHS

Hard-working # Driven by Challenges

Eye for detail # Motivator & Leader

TECHNOLOGIES

Blockchain Stream Keras Tensorflow

OpenCV </>
ML packages

TOOLS

</> VSCode </> RStudio > Terminal

Docker 😅 Jenkins 🤌 Git

🕰 JupyterLab 🗱 Slack 🔃 Trello

ACTIVITIES





OPERATING SYSTEMS





